<resources>
    //conver 1 Unidad1
    <string name="uno1">José: Hello. I’m José Villa. What’s your name?</string>
    <string name="ddos1"> Diana: Diana Pérez</string>
    <string name="tres1">José: It’s nice to meet you, Diana.</string>
    <string name="cuatro1">Diana: Nice to meet you too.</string>
    <string name="cinco1">José: I’m sorry. How do you spell your last name?</string>
    <string name="seis1">Diana: It’s P-E-R-E-Z</string>
    <string name="siete1">José: What do you do?</string>
    <string name="ocho1">Diana: I work as a personal assistant to the marketing director of SHIBITA</string>
    <string name="nueve1">José: What does your job involve?</string>
    <string name="diez1">Diana: I deal with new brands and I’m in charge of launching their products.</string>
    <string name="once1">José: Interesting. I am a sales manager, and I am looking for a company that advertises a new product.</string>
    <string name="doce1">Diana: Well, this is the right place for that. Here’s my business card, give me a call and let’s talk about it. </string>
    <string name="trece1">José: Thanks. I’ll sure do. It’s time to get back to the conference. </string>
    //conver 2 Unidad1


    <string name="app_name">MSEP</string>


    <string name="uno">Benjamin: Good morning, Sarah. How are you?</string>
    <string name="ddos">Sarah: I’m just fine. Thanks. Look, we have a visitor today, this is Carlos Mendoza. </string>
    <string name="tres">Benjamín: Hello Carlos. Do you work in the Chalatenango office?</string>
    <string name="cuatro">Carlos: Not right now. Only my boss is there. I’m established in La Paz for the moment</string>
    <string name="cinco">Benjamín: Look Michelle is coming. She’s based in La Paz too. Do you know her?</string>
    <string name="seis">Carlos: Oh, yes. We are creating a new brand.</string>
    <string name="siete">Sarah: Lucky you. She’s one of the best in the marketing area of this company.</string>
    <string name="ocho">Benjamin: Well. I have to run now for a meeting. Nice to meet you Carlos. See you guys later.</string>
    <string name="nueve">Carlos: My pleasure</string>
    <string name="diez">Sarah: Bye-bye.</string>
    //conver 3 Unidad1
    <string name="uno3">Boss: Good morning, everyone. Welcome to the promotion department. My name is Ana Cortéz,
        and I am your boss. I already know your names from the recruiting process, and I also can see them in your badges; however,
        I would like you to say something about the job you will be performing here and your main responsibilities. Pedro,
        would you like to start?</string>
    <string name="ddos3">Pedro: Sure. I’m Pedro González and I will be the manager consultant my main role here is to give advice on our markets, our organization,
        and our processes. I will be interviewing clients, identifying problems, and giving solutions. </string>
    <string name="tres3">Carmen: Good morning. My name is Carmen Villanueva and I am the accountant. Mainly I will be in charge of providing advice to the manager
        director on financial matters.I will be controlling the money that comes in and goes out. </string>
    <string name="cuatro3">Alex: Hello. I’m Alex Pineda. I’m glad to be here. Let me tell you that I am the quality manager and I arrange and carry out tests of our
        products and I deal with customers´ complaints. </string>
    //conver 1 unidad 2

    <string name="unou2">Sandy: Hello. </string>
    <string name="ddosu2"> David: Hi Sandy. It´s me David.</string>
    <string name="tresu2">Sandy: Hi. How are things in Portugal?</string>
    <string name="cuatrou2">David: Everything is fine. How about you?</string>
    <string name="cincou2">Sandy: I’m good. Where are you calling from?</string>
    <string name="seisu2">David: I’m in Porto at the moment. Listen, I’m calling because I need a favor.</string>
    <string name="sieteu2">Sandy: Sure. What do you need?</string>
    <string name="ochou2">David: I’m currently working on the plans for the new city mall, and I need you to email me the budget because
        I would like to reconsider some goods for the building. </string>
    <string name="nueveu2">Sandy: Right now, I’m finishing a financial report for Richard, so as soon as I’m done with it, I’ll send it to you.</string>
    <string name="diezu2">David: Thanks a lot. </string>
    <string name="onceu2">Sandy: See you soon. </string>
    //conver 2 unidad 2

    <string name="unou22">Robert: Good afternoon, Hellen.  </string>
    <string name="ddosu22"> Hellen: Good afternoon, Robert. I need to talk to you about the design for the new logo for Shibita. When can we meet?</string>
    <string name="tresu22">Robert: Sorry. I can’t make it today. I got meetings the rest of the afternoon. How about Tuesday morning?</string>
    <string name="cuatrou22">Hellen: I’m interviewing new sale reps on Tuesday morning, but the afternoon is fine.</string>
    <string name="cincou22">Robert: Actually, I have a medical appointment in the afternoon. Sorry. </string>
    <string name="seisu22">Hellen: OK. Let me see… Are you free on Wednesday?</string>
    <string name="sieteu22">Robert: No, I’m visiting clients on Wednesday morning and unfortunately, I’m flying to Costa Rica in the afternoon that day.</string>
    <string name="ochou22">Hellen: I see. So, are you going to the Marketing Fever Fair? </string>
    <string name="nueveu22">Robert: Of course. That’s on Thursday and Friday, but I’ll be back on Friday evening. </string>
    <string name="diezu22">Hellen: So, what about Monday morning? </string>
    <string name="onceu22">Robert: It sounds good to me. We can talk about it then. The coffee is on me. I have to go I have a meeting with the finance director. </string>
    <string name="doceu22">Hellen: Deal. See you then. </string>
    <string name="treceu22">Robert: Take care.  </string>
    //conver 3 unidad 2

    <string name="unou23">Bruno: Are we planning to go to the Marketing Fever Fair this year? </string>
    <string name="ddosu23"> Monica: Yes, I think so. It’s always a good place for making new clients and contacts. When is it?</string>
    <string name="tresu23">Bruno: It’s on the last week of March this year, from Wednesday to Friday.</string>
    <string name="cuatrou23">Monica: Oh! Wait a minute. Aren’t we going to Panama that week?</string>
    <string name="cincou23">Bruno: No. The Panama training is in May. </string>
    <string name="seisu23">Monica: That’s right. We are free to go to the Marketing Fever Fair then. </string>
    <string name="sieteu23">Bruno: Remember that they always do an awesome reception the first day.</string>
    <string name="ochou23">Monica: Sounds great. Can you make all the necessary arrangements? </string>
    <string name="nueveu23">Bruno: No problem. I’ll buy our tickets, book the hotel, and confirm our attendance. </string>
    <string name="diezu23">Monica: Perfect.  </string>
    //conver 1 unidad 3
    <string name="unou3c11">Mike: Hi! Rosa. Welcome back. </string>
    <string name="ddosu3c12"> Rosa: Hey, hi! What´s new?</string>
    <string name="tresu3c13">Mike: Well, the new management have decided to invest in staff training.</string>
    <string name="cuatro3c14">Rosa: Oh, really? Those are good news. What are the trainings about?</string>
    <string name="cinco3c15">Mike: Our managers want us to improve our performance when presenting and negotiating with suppliers
        and clients and make the most of our computer skills. </string>
    <string name="seis3c16">Rosa: That´s great! In my case, I have been meaning to get better at my computer skills </string>
    <string name="siete3c17">Mike: Good for you, in my case I’ll be working on my negotiating skills.</string>
    <string name="ocho3c18">Rosa: Let´s do it.</string>
    //conver 2 unidad 3
    <string name="unou3c21">Bruno: Good news, our booking for the marketing fever fair has been confirmed. </string>
    <string name="ddosu3c22"> Monica: Excellent! Now it´s time to organize the stand. By the way, do you know where it is?</string>
    <string name="tresu3c23">Bruno: Let me check my email, I got it yesterday. It´s in Conference Room 2.</string>
    <string name="cuatro3c24">Monica: Lucky you! That´s one of the best Conference Rooms. This exhibition is going to be better than last year.</string>
    <string name="cinco3c25">Bruno: Can´t wait. I´m sure that there will be more visitors than last year. </string>
    <string name="seis3c26">Monica: Let´s get started then. </string>
    //conver 3 unidad 3
    <string name="unou3c31">Monica: Bruno, where are the snacks? The people from the hotel promised to bring them at 9:00 AM, are they here yet? </string>
    <string name="ddosu3c32"> Bruno: Actually no. I´ll call them now.</string>
    <string name="tresu3c33">Bruno: Hello, this is Bruno Marin from Conference Room 2..</string>
    <string name="cuatro3c34">Receptionist: How can I help you, Mr. Marin?</string>
    <string name="cinco3c35">Bruno: We asked for 150 snacks, and you promised that they will be here at 9:00, but it´s 9:30 there is no sight of them. </string>
    <string name="seis3c36">Receptionist: I´m really sorry for the inconvenience Mr. Marin, let me assist you right away, can you hold for a minute? </string>
    <string name="sieteu3c37">Bruno: yes. I´ll hold.</string>
    <string name="ocho3c38">Receptionist: Thank you for your patience, let me inform you that the inconvenience with the snacks has been solved. They are on the way to your Conference Room as we speak.</string>
    <string name="nueve3c39">Bruno: Thanks a lot! I appreciate your help. </string>
    <string name="diezc310">Receptionist: For the inconvenience the hotel will give you a 25% off. Have a nice day Mr. Marin.</string>
    //conver 1 unidad 4

    <string name="unou4c11">Bryan: Computer Supplies Ltd, May I help you? </string>
    <string name="ddosu4c12"> Wendy: Hello, I would like to speak to Andrea Roja please?</string>
    <string name="tresu4c13">Bryan: Who´s calling, please?</string>
    <string name="cuatro4c14">Wendy: This is Wendy Castro, of VECAS import.</string>
    <string name="cinco4c15">Bryan: Sorry, Ms. Roja is not at the office at this moment, would you like to leave a message? </string>
    <string name="seis4c16">Wendy: Yes. Our order has just arrived, and you sent the wrong computer parts. We ordered 6 SSD hard drives, 6 pairs of DDR4 memory RAM, 12 Power supplies for servers, 12 RTX 2016 TI video cards. You sent us 4 SSD hard drives, 4 pairs of DDR4 memory RAM, 12 power supplies for computers and 12 TRX 2016 video cards. </string>
    <string name="siete4c17">Bryan: I see, can you give me your order number?</string>
    <string name="ocho4c18">Wendy: Sure. It´s 2021-0111-99.</string>
    <string name="nueve4u19">Bryan: Can you please hold while I am checking your order.</string>
    <string name="diezu4u110">Wendy: Take your time.</string>
    <string name="once4u111">Bryan: Thanks for holding Ms. Castro. We apologize for the inconvenience; I can see that the wrong computer parts were sent. I´ll pass your message to Ms. Roja to take care of your order. She will contact you ASAP.</string>
    <string name="doce4u112">Wendy: I appreciate your help. I´ll keep an eye out for that, thanks.</string>
    //conver 2 unidad 4
    <string name="unou4c21">Robert: Welcome to Pinewood taxes, how may I help you? </string>
    <string name="ddosu4c22"> Linda: I would like someone to assist me with my income taxes.</string>
    <string name="tresu4c23">Robert: Glad to. First, we need your Employee Wage Report Form. Do you have it with you?</string>
    <string name="cuatro4c24">Linda: Yes, I do.</string>
    <string name="cinco4c25">Robert: Great! Let me see it, so I can get started on your taxes.</string>
    <string name="seis4c26">Linda: Last time, I paid a huge amount of money back and I never understood why. So I wonder if you can explain to me what this is about?</string>
    <string name="siete4c27">Robert: Well, every month part of your income is taken out of your paycheck by the IRS.</string>
    <string name="ocho4c28">Linda: Oh! Do you mean the federal and State taxes?</string>
    <string name="nueve4u29">Robert: Exactly. And what we are doing here is checking to see if you paid too much or too little to the IRS last year.</string>
    <string name="diezu4u210">Linda: I hope I can get a big refund with your help this time, let´s do it.</string>
    //conver 3 unidad 4
    <string name="unou4c31">Natalia: Pixel Electronics</string>
    <string name="ddosu4c32">Henry: Good morning, I would like to speak to Natalia Garcia.</string>
    <string name="tresu4c33">Natalia: Speaking.</string>
    <string name="cuatro4c34">Henry: This is Henry. You forgot to email me the budget figures, and the meeting has just started. I need them right now.</string>
    <string name="cinco4c35">Natalia: Well, you are not going to like this, but my assistant found out that some of the figures aren’t quite right. I hope they will be ready in an hour.</string>
    <string name="seis4c36">Henry: That´s very irresponsible from your side. I´ll try to delay this presentation as much as possible, however; if they are not ready by the time they need to be presented, you will need to report to our Regional Director.</string>
    <string name="siete4c37">Linda: We are doing everything we can to fix the issue so we don’t get to that point. You must know that we had a problem with our cloud service.</string>
    <string name="ocho4c38">Henry: Did you contact the IT department so they can help you fix the problem?</string>
    <string name="nueve4u39">Linda: Of course, Marcos is working on that, we’ll let you know when everything is worked out.</string>
    <string name="diezu4u310">Henry: OK.</string>
    //conver 1 unidad 5

    <string name="unou5c11">Diana: Hey! You look familiar </string>
    <string name="ddosu5c12"> Juan: You too. Aren´t Diana Medina from The First Bank?</string>
    <string name="tresu5c13">Diana: Right. Juan Cortez, isn´t it?</string>
    <string name="cuatrou5c14">Juan: Flesh and blood. .</string>
    <string name="cincou5c15">Diana: I remember that I interviewed a few years ago; we offered you a job but you decided to work with Main Bank instead. </string>
    <string name="seisu5c16">Juan: Yeah, I did that, sorry, the thing is that they offered me better conditions.  </string>
    <string name="sieteu5c17">Diana: I got it. How are things there then?</string>
    <string name="ochou5c18">Juan: It didn´t work out for me, so after a year I quit, and I decided to start my own Advertising Company.</string>
    <string name="nueveu5c19">Diana: Good for you. How is your company doing so far?</string>
    <string name="diezu5c110">Juan: Right now, we are looking for a bank loan to purchase new high tech multimedia equipment.</string>
    <string name="onceu5c111">Diana: You must give me your business card.</string>
    <string name="doceu5c112">Juan: Here it is.</string>
    <string name="treceu5c113">Diana: Let´s keep in touch.</string>

    //conver 2 unidad 5
    <string name="unou5c21">Bank Manager: All the paperwork has been checked by loan department and any observations were found. We are just missing to take a look to your
        business plan. What can you tell me about it?</string>
    <string name="ddosu5c22"> Juan: There are several advertising companies already, so we are looking to step up from the current Salvadorean market and we are going to
        offer advertising campaigns based on augmented reality technology.  </string>
    <string name="tresu5c23">BM: I understand that you already have part of the multimedia equipment needed to accomplish that.</string>
    <string name="cuatrou5c24">Juan: Yes. However, that equipment is out of date, and it won’t help us to expand our range quickly.</string>
    <string name="cincou5c25">BM: What kind of companies are going to be your main market?</string>
    <string name="seisu5c26">Juan: Companies that target young people, like clothing, shoes, video games and so on.</string>
    <string name="sieteu5c27">BM: Let´s look at these sales figures in more detail.</string>
    <string name="ochou5c28">Juan: alright, you won’t get disappointed.</string>

    //conver 3 unidad 5
    <string name="unou5c31">Silvia: Welcome to another episode of Marketing Plus, my name is Silvia and today we are going to know a little bit about Juan who is crated an amazing advertising agency. Juan is the founder
        of 60 sec marketing, it´s good to have you here Juan. So tell us what makes your company different from the rest?</string>
    <string name="ddosu5c32">Juan: We offer implementation, strategy, training and workshops, but for the first time in history in El Salvador, all our services are based on augmented reality.</string>
    <string name="tresu5c33">Silvia: WOW! Interesting, where can we have a piece of your artwork and see it working?</string>
    <string name="cuatrou5c34">Juan: In this moment we are working with a clothing store and in a couples of weeks you will see the biggest campaign with this new way of doing marketing here in our country.</string>
    <string name="cincou5c35">Silvia: Can´t wait to see that, can you give us a heads up here for our audience?</string>
    <string name="seisu5c36">Juan: I am sorry, I can´t, we have signed a confidentially paper, but I promise you that the waiting will be worthy.</string>
    <string name="sieteu5c37">Silvia: We will definitely keep an eye on that, and we will see you soon that expected.</string>
    <string name="ochou5c38">Juan: Thank you for the opportunity for spreading the good news of this new technology in marketing.</string>
    <string name="nueveu5c39">Silvia: Thank you for listening us, see you next time, stay tuned.</string>

</resources>
